Yuito.
結人
This is the only way.
只能這麼做了
Karen!
卡連
Stand aside, Fubiki.
吹雪 走開
Karen, just stop.
卡連 住手吧
I never knew you were in so much pain.
沒想到 你這麼痛苦
Shut it.
閉嘴
That's enough. You've done enough.
夠了 已經夠了
I...
我…
Both Alice and I wouldn't want you to be in so much pain.
我和愛麗絲… 都不希望看到你這麼痛苦
Shut it!
閉嘴
Karen!
卡連
We must live on in this world.
我們必須在這個世界活下去
We must live on in the world without Alice.
在沒有愛麗絲的世界 活下去
I understand how you feel.
我理解你的心情
But we must accept the reality.
但是 我們只能接受
Learn to accept it now and live on.
現在開始接受 並且活下去
Karen, please.
卡連 拜託你
We need your help.
請你協助我們
We need to reach Chronos Terminal
到克洛諾斯航站
and undo the dimensional entanglement you created.
解開因你而產生的維度糾纏
I don't want to forsake our future.
我不希望關閉前往未來的道路
I can never let that happen.
絕不能讓這件事發生
Stop resisting.
別在掙扎了
We are doing this for those who care about you.
這麼做也是為那些擔心你的人
I see.
是嗎…
Is this the end?
這裡…就是終結嗎…
In that case, this is still an option.
那麼 這也是一種…選擇嗎…
Yuito...
結人
SCARLET NEXUS
《緋紅結繫》
♫Felling of tiredness is losing yourself♫
倦怠感 losing yourself
♫How do you still create a relationship each other♫
尚未找到建立關係的方法嗎
♫It’s my awkward friend’s fault♫
有個麻煩的朋友
♫Until death, wanting someone somewhere to embrace me♫
至死都在尋求某人的擁抱
♫While the devil is not here and between the chaos♫
在得以喘息的混沌虛無之間
♫Aiming between win and lose♫
以輸贏之間為目標
♫Not to be running out of patience for now, I’m trying to be careful♫
注意別讓信任走向盡頭 務必小心
♫You’ll see I’m always on your side♫
You'll see I'm always on your side
♫I tried hard to connect today as well♫
今天仍拼命地聯繫著
♫You’re frigid and your roller coaster inside the brain♫
你腦中那冷感的軌道
♫The grungy days and the unprecedented catastrophy♫
搖滾的日子未曾有過的浩劫
♫Where is the glory buried?♫
光榮早已埋葬在某處
♫The lonely monster in a moment♫
這一瞬間寂寞孤獨的野獸
♫The bullet shot by the machinegun goes parallelly♫
與機關槍射出的子彈並列
♫To pierce with the theory♫
射穿所有世間道理
♫I tried hard to connect today as well♫
今天仍拼命地聯繫著
♫The bullet shot by the machinegun goes parallelly♫
與機關槍射出的子彈並列
♫I tried hard to connect today as well♫
今天也仍在一起 清晰地聯繫著
♫You’re frigid and the theory in the brain♫
你那腦中冷感的正義
OPERATION KUNAD GATE
(消滅岐之門作戰)
Hey, how is the data you're getting?
喂 你那邊的資料顯示如何
It doesn't work, the data is useless.
不行 無法資料化了
This growth is incredible.
這個成長速度到底是…
At this rate...
再這樣下去…
We can no longer observe.
超過觀察極限了
Damn it!
可惡
-What's wrong? -It's gone.
-怎麼回事 -消失了
-The system... -It's shutting down!
-系統… -當機了
OFFLINE
(機能停止)
There is nothing more that we can do.
我們…已經無能為力了
Good morning.
早安
Fubuki...
吹雪
Should a Major General be here?
連隊長在這裡好嗎
Consider yourself a lucky one.
這算是不幸中的大幸吧
The Others are surprisingly idle for the moment.
怪異現在莫名的安分
I wonder if they are just as scared.
怪異 是否也在害怕呢
Alice once said
愛麗絲 以前說過
you should smile more often
卡連應該要經常笑
because she thought your smile was great.
因為你的笑容很不錯
But you never smiled again after that day.
從那天開始 你就不再笑了
Well, you barely smiled even before that.
雖然 你本來就不常笑
I don't think I can heal the wound in your heart.
我不認為我能治癒你的心
Even so, I still hope
但我還是希望
you can live your own life.
你能好好走完你的人生
I believe that one day, you will
總有一天 你定能在這個世上
smile again.
再次露出笑容
Will undoing the entanglement
解開維度糾纏
destroy the Kunad Gate?
讓岐之門消失就好了嗎
Fubuki.
吹雪
You should have noticed by now.
如果是你 應該察覺到了吧
Major General Fubuki.
吹雪連隊長
You're awake.
你醒啦
Karen.
卡連
We need your power for the operation.
執行作戰時 需要你的力量
Well, can you join us?
如何 可以嗎
Operation?
作戰…
Did you forget why you fought me?
你們是為了什麼與我戰鬥的
To destroy the Kunad Gate.
為了岐之門
Yes, but things aren't that simple.
對 但事情並非這麼簡單
We need to destroy the Extinction Belt too.
還必須消滅斷絕之帶
The Extinction Belt too?
消滅斷絕之帶
Kaito once proposed a plan of letting the Kunad Gate absorb the Extinction Belt.
界人皇曾提案讓岐之門 吸收斷絕之帶的計畫
Yes, but that is not possible.
是的 但這是不可能的
Even with the gravity manipulation by Kasane and I,
因為我和重使用操縱重力的腦力
we still couldn't make it happen.
也無法達到那個效果
Are you saying...
難道…
We'll connect the people's minds
連結全國民的腦部
and increase the output of your power.
增強超腦力的強度
But that's not the only way.
但其實不必這麼做
We can connect to Arahabaki as well.
只要連結荒吐神也行
The whole city has gone offline,
雖然都市機能癱瘓了
but Arahabaki is still operational.
但荒吐神目前還正常運作
We can boost your power via a connection with SAS.
用SAS連結 就有可能提升超腦力
Arahabaki has spent the past few centuries running some kind of simulation.
荒吐神花了數百年的時間 一直在做某種模擬狀況
Really?
竟然有這種事
However, something still concerns me.
不過 有件事較令人擔心
Will you and Kasane be able to withstand the power output from Arahabaki?
那就是你們兩人能否承受得住 荒吐神增強後的力道
Even if the chance is slim,
只要有一點可能
I'm willing to give it a shot.
我都願意嘗試
It's decided, then.
那就這麼決定了
Your plan is to destroy both the Kunad Gate and the Extinction Belt?
同時消除岐之門和斷絕之帶
If the plan works, countless lives can be saved.
如果成功的話 就能拯救無數的生命
No, it'll be too much for Yuito's body.
不行 結人的身體已經到極限了
Who knows what will happen if he pushes himself too hard?
再繼續逞強不知會如何…
Don't you agree?
大家也這麼覺得吧
Hanabi is right.
花火說得沒錯
We can't Yuito join the operation.
不能讓結人參加
But even with the connection to Arahabaki that increases power output,
不過 就算連結荒吐神來增強腦力
are Kasane and Karen strong enough to move the Extinction Belt?
只靠重和卡連 真的能移動斷絕之帶嗎
Honestly, I still can't imagine
老實說 我無法想像
how we are going to move the Extinction Belt.
要如何移動斷絕之帶
It's better to think of this as the one last chance we have.
最好做好機會只有一次的打算
Put all of your strength into it.
一口氣使出最大力量
We won't have time to wait and observe.
沒有時間看狀況了
But...
可是…
Yuito.
結人
Sorry for the long wait, everyone.
各位 久等了
Yuito, you look pale.
結人 你的臉色好差
You shouldn't be out of your bed.
你得繼續休息才行啊
Don't worry about me.
不用擔心我
Don't be silly.
說什麼傻話
You can barely stand straight.
你現在站著都很吃力了
Hanabi, I'm going.
花火 我要去
Everyone will support me through SAS.
大家會透過SAS協助我們吧
It won't be a problem.
所以 沒問題的
Do you have a death wish?
你…想死嗎
You're always pushing yourself so hard.
你總是這麼逞強
Do you really think throwing your life away will solve all the problems?
是不是覺得自己死了 一切都解決了
Don't be such a fool.
開什麼玩笑
We've gone through hell to make it this far.
我們是多麼努力才走到現在
But you,
現在也是
you are still going to risk your life for the operation no matter what we say.
不論我們說什麼 你都堅持參加作戰吧
Sorry.
抱歉…
There is one thing we need to do.
那我們要做的事只有一件
No matter what Yuito do,
不論結人多逞強
we cannot let him die.
都不能讓結人死
Hanabi.
花火
Thank you, Hanabi.
謝謝妳 花火
OSF of Suoh
蘇芳怪伐軍
has reached the defense position along with the Seiran force.
與青藍軍隊 抵達防守位置
Understood.
知道了
Standby for the next order.
下個指示來之前先待命
Roger.
了解
Let me make this clear.
我先聲明
I'm letting you copy my power because it's absolutely necessary.
因為有必要所以才讓你複製腦力
Don't you dare backstab us.
不許有其他企圖
I assure you,
別擔心
I'll help you realize your goal.
我會實現你們的願望
Brother...
哥哥
Even my little brother doubts me.
連弟弟都懷疑我嗎
No, that's not what I meant.
不 不是這樣的
Don't worry, the operation will be a success.
放心吧 我會讓作戰成功的
I'll hold you to that.
一定喔
So, is everything ready?
那麼 準備好了嗎
The connection to Arahabaki is ready,
準備好與荒吐神連結了
we can proceed at any time.
隨時可以連結
We'll be connected to SAS to provide support.
這次我們也會連結SAS 協助你們
Let's make it happen, Yuito, Kasane!
一起加油吧 重 結人
-Yes. -Sure.
-好
The process will put a strain on everyone.
我想可能會給大家帶來很大的負擔
But please lend me your strength.
但請大家借我力量
We can do this.
相信一定會順利的
We'll make it work.
我們一定做得到
After all, we've worked together so many times.
畢竟我們合力了這麼多次
Everyone, let's do this!
各位 開始吧
SAS connection to Arahabaki, commence!
荒吐神 SAS連結 開始
This is...
這是…
OSF of Suoh and Seiran forces,
蘇芳怪伐軍和青藍軍隊 聽好
the Others are idle for now,
雖然怪異現在很安分
but they might start attacking anytime.
但不知他們何時會開始活動
The best we can do for New Himuka and this world
現在我們能為新日向 能為世界做的事
is to protect them.
就是守護他們
Do not let any enemy break through our ranks!
不准讓任何怪異越雷池一步
Yes!
是
First thing first, the Extinction Belt.
首先 是斷絕之帶
Yes.
好
No movement was detected from the Extinction Belt.
斷絕之帶 目前沒有反應
The connection with Arahabaki is unstable.
與荒吐神的連結並不穩定
Yuito, Kasane, focus!
結人 重 集中精神
Understood! I must control this power...
我知道 得操控這股力量…
Move, now!
快點動啊
Yes, it's moving.
很好 開始動了
But if we lost focus for even a split-second...
不過 稍不注意意識就…
Let's show this thing what we've got.
我們不能示弱啊…
Give me the power to control Arahabaki.
交給我操控荒吐神的力量吧
I've been connected to it for 2000 years. I can handle it.
我與荒吐神連結了2000年 應該沒問題
-Karen... -We'll leave it to you.
-卡連 -拜託你了
-Kasane! -Yes!
-重 -好
The Extinction Belt...
斷絕之帶…
Is it working?
行得通嗎
Yes! The Extinction Belt is being absorbed by the Kunad Gate!
很好 斷絕之帶 正在被岐之門吸收
Amazing.
好厲害
Be gone!
就這樣消失吧
-Is it working? -Yes!
-會成功嗎 -很好
Yuito...
結人
-No! -The Extinction Belt...
-糟糕 -斷絕之帶…
Things took a turn for the worst.
變成最糟糕的狀態了
Go into formation and get ready to battle!
改變陣型 準備迎戰
Yuito!
結人
Yuito...
結人…
Sorry, I...
抱歉 我…
It's all right. Can you keep up?
沒事 還能繼續嗎
Yes.
能
This is the last push!
這是最後了
Show me all you have!
讓我看看你的氣勢
Yuito, you can do it.
結人 加油
Take our strength with you!
接收我們的力量吧
If you want to save the world,
既然你說想拯救這個世界
then show me!
那就證明給我看
Go!
去吧
The Extinction Belt is gone.
斷絕之帶 消失了
Don't celebrate too soon.
要高興還太早了
Now we must proceed to Chronos Terminal
接下來要去克洛諾斯航站
and undo the last entanglement.
解開最後的維度糾纏
Yeah.
是啊
That won't be necessary.
沒這個必要
Karen!
卡連
Brother!
哥哥
I just can't give it up.
我還是無法放棄
What are you trying to do?
你想做什麼
No!
不…不行…
Wait!
等等
I told you I would help you realize your goal.
我說過會實現你們的願望吧
Therefore, I will no longer act as Yakumo Sumeragi.
所以 我已經不打算成為八雲皇了
This is the final time travel.
這是…最後一次的時間跳躍
-He's out of line again. -Karen...
-又擅自做決定 -卡連
Brother...
哥哥
Red Strings reactions have been detected throughout Suoh!
整個蘇芳都有紅色繫線的反應
But how?
怎麼會…
The same reaction was detected in Seiran and Togetsu too.
青藍和渡月也有相同反應
I think he's expanded a massive barrier.
我想 可能是展開了超廣領域
What happened?
到底發生什麼事了
Look, Yuito.
結人 快看
The Kunad Gate...
岐之門…
The sky looks beautiful.
好漂亮
Did we make it?
我們…成功了嗎
We did it.
成功了
The sky is finally blue again.
天空…好蔚藍啊
Brother...
哥哥
Were those red threads the manifestation of the Red Strings?
剛才的紅絲線 就是紅色繫線的力量嗎
Karen went back in time
卡連回到過去
and somehow changed the world.
對世界造成了某種影響吧
Did anything else change aside from the Kunad Gate?
除了岐之門消失之外 還有其他變化嗎…
I got carried away.
不小心看入迷了
I'm running a diagnosis right now.
我馬上調查
Haruka, let's do this.
遙 開始吧
I'm way ahead of you, Brother.
我早就已經開始了 哥哥
We managed to protect the world.
我們成功保護世界了吧
Not only did we change the future,
我們不只是救了未來
we even destroyed the Extinction Belt.
還消滅了斷絕之帶
We did it with Karen's help.
是我們 和卡連努力的結果
We created a new future.
我們創造出新的未來
Karen, are you looking at this azure sky too?
卡連 你也正在某處 看著這片天空嗎
-Yes! -We're saved!
-好耶 -得救了
♫I'm troubled by my own yearning♫
被追求的憧憬所困
♫Unveil the blocked sun ray♫
揭開被阻擋的搖曳陽炎
♫There's a stranger in me♫
There's a stranger in me
♫That I've never seen♫
從未見過
♫I can not soar in the sky without fear♫
自己能不再恐懼翱翔高空
♫I'm spreading my wings♫
I'm spreading my wings
♫Dancing gracefully like a bird♫
華麗舞步的鳥兒
♫And gazing towards the scarlet sky♫
仰望染紅的天空
♫I chased after the gust♫
追過了強風
♫The scenery spreads into the ever-changing world♫
景色蔓延在千變萬化的世界裡
♫Inside the intertwined brilliance♫
在交錯的光芒中
♫I'm still searching for tomorrow's direction♫
持續尋找明天的行徑方向
♫Tomorrow's in your hands♫
Tomorrow's in your hands
♫Don't tell me now you're afraid♫
Don't tell me now you're afraid
♫There's no time to waste♫
There's no time to waste
♫Go forward♫
前進
♫Have no fear for anything♫
不再畏懼何物
♫Now, let's go♫
走吧
♫Into a brand new day♫
Into a brand new day
What is going on?
這是怎麼回事
There is no data about Karen anywhere.
完全沒有跟卡連相關的情報
Yes, we've run it multiple times.
沒錯 我們查了很多次…
Major General Fubuki!
吹雪連隊長
Was the operation a success?
作戰 作戰成功了吧
Yes.
是啊…
Great!
太好了
You did it, Fubuki.
成功了 吹雪
Alice...
愛…愛麗絲…
Why? You look surprised.
怎麼了 為何這麼驚訝
But...
不…
Hanabi, you're all right.
花火 妳也沒事啊
I'm glad to see you.
太好了
Thank you...
謝…謝謝…
Alice, how did you...
愛麗絲 妳…
No.
不
There's something I must confirm.
我想先確認一件事
It's about Karen...
關於…卡連的事…
Fubuki,
吹雪
who is Karen?
卡連…是誰啊
EVERYONE'S FUTURE
(各自的未來)